export const regularVerbsGame = {
  gameId: 2,
  type: 'TranslationGame',
  name: 'Regular Verbs',
  instructions: 'Translate the verb into all tenses.',
  actions: [
    { placeholder: 'Infinitive', label: 'Infinitive' },
    { placeholder: 'Past and participle', label: 'Past/participle' }
  ],
  questions: [
    {
      prompt: 'Aceptar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Accept' }, { value: 'Accepted' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Contar', answers: [{ value: 'Count' }, { value: 'Counted' }] },
    { prompt: 'Citar', answers: [{ value: 'Date' }, { value: 'Dated' }] },
    { prompt: 'Terminar', answers: [{ value: 'End' }, { value: 'Ended' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Esperar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Expect' }, { value: 'Expected' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Intentar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Intend' }, { value: 'Intended' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Necesitar', answers: [{ value: 'Need' }, { value: 'Needed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Plantar', answers: [{ value: 'Plant' }, { value: 'Planted' }] },
    { prompt: 'Señalar', answers: [{ value: 'Point' }, { value: 'Pointed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Rentar', answers: [{ value: 'Rent' }, { value: 'Rented' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Repetir',
      answers: [{ value: 'Repeat' }, { value: 'Repeated' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Resistir',
      answers: [{ value: 'Resist' }, { value: 'Resisted' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Empezar', answers: [{ value: 'Start' }, { value: 'Started' }] },
    { prompt: 'Visitar', answers: [{ value: 'Visit' }, { value: 'Visited' }] },
    { prompt: 'Esperar', answers: [{ value: 'Wait' }, { value: 'Waited' }] },
    { prompt: 'Querer', answers: [{ value: 'Want' }, { value: 'Wanted' }] },
    { prompt: 'Preguntar', answers: [{ value: 'Ask' }, { value: 'Asked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Cocinar', answers: [{ value: 'Cook' }, { value: 'Cooked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Bailar', answers: [{ value: 'Dance' }, { value: 'Danced' }] },
    { prompt: 'Vestir', answers: [{ value: 'Dress' }, { value: 'Dressed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Borrar', answers: [{ value: 'Erase' }, { value: 'Erased' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Terminar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Finish' }, { value: 'Finished' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Ayudar', answers: [{ value: 'Help' }, { value: 'Helped' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Saltar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Jump' }, { value: 'Jumped' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Gustar', answers: [{ value: 'Like' }, { value: 'Liked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Mirar', answers: [{ value: 'Look' }, { value: 'Looked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Extrañar', answers: [{ value: 'Miss' }, { value: 'Missed' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Practicar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Practice' }, { value: 'Practiced' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Empujar', answers: [{ value: 'Push' }, { value: 'Pushed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Comprar', answers: [{ value: 'Shop' }, { value: 'Shopped' }] },
    { prompt: 'Fumar', answers: [{ value: 'Smoke' }, { value: 'Smoked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Detener', answers: [{ value: 'Stop' }, { value: 'Stopped' }] },
    { prompt: 'Hablar', answers: [{ value: 'Talk' }, { value: 'Talked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Usar', answers: [{ value: 'Use' }, { value: 'Used' }] },
    { prompt: 'Caminar', answers: [{ value: 'Walk' }, { value: 'Walked' }] },
    { prompt: 'Lavar', answers: [{ value: 'Wash' }, { value: 'Washed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Desear', answers: [{ value: 'Wish' }, { value: 'Wished' }] },
    { prompt: 'Trabajar', answers: [{ value: 'Work' }, { value: 'Worked' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Responder',
      answers: [{ value: 'Answer' }, { value: 'Answered' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Llegar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Arrive' }, { value: 'Arrived' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Pertenecer',
      answers: [{ value: 'Belong' }, { value: 'Belonged' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Cambiar', answers: [{ value: 'Change' }, { value: 'Changed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Limpiar', answers: [{ value: 'Clean' }, { value: 'Cleaned' }] },
    { prompt: 'Escalar', answers: [{ value: 'Climb' }, { value: 'Climbed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Cerrar', answers: [{ value: 'Close' }, { value: 'Closed' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Considerar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Consider' }, { value: 'Considered' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Retar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Dare' }, { value: 'Dared' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Entregar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Deliver' }, { value: 'Delivered' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Disfrutar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Enjoy' }, { value: 'Enjoyed' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Llenar', answers: [{ value: 'Fill' }, { value: 'Filled' }] },
    { prompt: 'Seguir', answers: [{ value: 'Follow' }, { value: 'Followed' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Apurar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Hurry' }, { value: 'Hurried' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Aprender', answers: [{ value: 'Learn' }, { value: 'Learned' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Escuchar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Listen' }, { value: 'Listened' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Vivir', answers: [{ value: 'Live' }, { value: 'Lived' }] },
    { prompt: 'Amar', answers: [{ value: 'Love' }, { value: 'Loved' }] },
    { prompt: 'Nombrar', answers: [{ value: 'Name' }, { value: 'Named' }] },
    { prompt: 'Abrir', answers: [{ value: 'Open' }, { value: 'Opened' }] },
    { prompt: 'Ordenar', answers: [{ value: 'Order' }, { value: 'Ordered' }] },
    { prompt: 'Planear', answers: [{ value: 'Plan' }, { value: 'Planed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Jugar', answers: [{ value: 'Play' }, { value: 'Played' }] },
    { prompt: 'Llover', answers: [{ value: 'Rain' }, { value: 'Rained' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Recordar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Remember' }, { value: 'Remembered' }]
    },
    { prompt: 'Mostrar', answers: [{ value: 'Show' }, { value: 'Showed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Permanecer', answers: [{ value: 'Stay' }, { value: 'Stayed' }] },
    { prompt: 'Estudiar', answers: [{ value: 'Study' }, { value: 'Studied' }] },
    { prompt: 'Viajar', answers: [{ value: 'Travel' }, { value: 'Traveled' }] },
    {
      prompt: 'Intentar',
      answers: [{ value: 'Try' }, { value: 'Tried' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'Voltear',
      answers: [{ value: 'Turn' }, { value: 'Turned' }]
    }
  ]
}
